Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Department of Special Collections and University Archives, Records SC0756
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Exhibits Department Records, 1969-2010; Accession ARCH_2010_056; 32 Linear Feet; (22 boxes)
  - Zuancho: Unsodo Request Images and Woodblock loan (2008) (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Zuancho: Zuancho Facsimile Measurements and banner image size conversions (2008) (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Experiments in Navigation: The Art of Charles Hobson (April 30 -- August 17, 2008) Cantor Exhibit (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Hobson: Cantor -- Item List (2008) (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Hobson: Cantor -- Labels (2008) (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Hobson: Cantor -- Layout (2008) (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Hobson: Cantor -- Loans and Call Slips (2008) (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Hobson: Cantor -- Meeting Notes (2008) (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Hobson: Cantor -- TIFFS, Test Set (2008) (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Hobson: Case Maps (2008) (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Hobson: Catalog (2008) (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Bancroft Library, Twain Letter Repro. Permission (2008) (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Correspondence w/ CMH re: exhibit catalog (2008) (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Cover (2008) (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Distribution (2008) (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Ed. Notes (2008) (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Editorial Work, Folder 1 of 2 (2008) (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Editorial Work, Folder 2 of 2 (2008) (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Edits 11/21/07 (2008) (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Estimates and Invoices (2008) (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- First drafts (2008) (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- fold-down; pre-binding (2008) (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Index Print (2008) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- May Castleberry Intro (2008) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Old Drafts (2008) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Preliminary Design (2008) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Proposal (2008) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- RGT Preface (2008) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Sent to Charles 11/2/07 (2008) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Sent to Stinehour 2/28/08 (2008) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- TIFF Files, Sent to Stinehour 2/13/08 (2008) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Hobson: Catalog -- Use of Summerstone's Magma and Numa Types (2008) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Hobson: Charles Hobson (2008) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Hobson: Colors (2008) (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Hobson: Email Log (2008) (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Hobson: Glynn's Edits (2008) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Hobson: Green -- Kudos (2008) (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Hobson: Green -- Labels (2008) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Hobson: Green -- Texts/Glynn's (2008) (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Hobson: Planning mtgs w/ Glynn, Roberto, Charles (2008) (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Hobson: Production Schedule (2008) (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Hobson: Announcement (2008) (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Hobson: Announcement Mailing Labels (2008) (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Hobson: Event, May 2008 (2008) (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Hobson: Press Release (2008) (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Hobson: Publicity (2008) (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Hobson: Studio Visit (2008) (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Hobson: Texts (2008) (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - American Primers and Readers: Featuring the Words and Collection of Richard L. Venezky (Sept 15 -- Dec 31, 2008): Banners and Backdrops (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Venezky: Casemaps (2008) (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Venezky: Colors (2008) (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Venezky: Cubberly Exhibition (2008) (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Venezky: Donation in support of exhibit (2008) (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Venezky: Floorplan (2008) (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Venezky: Images/DLSS Scan Requests (2008) (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Venezky: Interview with Richard L. Venezky (2008) (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Venezky: Prep Sheets (2008) (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Venezky: Poster and Announcement PDF (2008) (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Venezky: Proposal and Correspondence (2008) (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Venezky: Publicity (2008) (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Venezky: Reception (2008) (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Venezky: Texts and Captions (2008) (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Notable Campus Canines (With a Nod to Cats): Stories from the Stanford University Archives (January 19 -- April 5, 2009): Alice (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Dogs: Carole Hyde's Talk on the History of PAHS (2009) (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Dogs: Case Layouts (2009) (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Dogs: DS Jordan (case 15) (2009) (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Dogs: Faculty (case 16) (2009) (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Dogs: Highwire (2009) (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Dogs: Leo Holub Loan (2009) (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Dogs: Misc. Notes and Email (2009) (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Dogs: Nod to Cats (case 19) (2009) (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Dogs: Not Used (2009) (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Dogs: Oscar and His Loose Companions (2009) (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Dogs: Pat White, Archives Exhibit (2009) (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Dogs: Postcard (2009) (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Dogs: Posters (2009) (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Dogs: Press Release and Publicity (2009) (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Dogs: Stanford Family (case 14) (2009) (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Dogs: Visitors Log (2009) (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Dogs: Working Dogs (case 18) (2009) (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - "All of This I Have Seen:" Leigh Ortenburger, Mountaineer and Photographer (January 12 -- April 5, 2009): Announcement (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Ortenburger: Book, 1 of 2 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Ortenburger: Book, 2 of 2 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Ortenburger: Case 1 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Ortenburger: Case 2 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Ortenburger: Case 3 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Ortenburger: Case 4 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Ortenburger: Case 5 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Ortenburger: Case 6 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Ortenburger: Case 7 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Ortenburger: Case 8 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Ortenburger: Case 9 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Ortenburger: Case 10 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Ortenburger: Case 11 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Ortenburger: Case 12 (2009) (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Ortenburger: Feb. 19 party for Dogs and Ortenburger Exhibits (2009) (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Ortenburger: Item Labels (2009) (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Ortenburger: Layout (2009) (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Ortenburger: Panorama (2009) (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Ortenburger: Panorama Lighting (2009) (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Ortenburger: Poster (2009) (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Ortenburger: Press Release and Publicity (2009) (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Ortenburger: Rawlings (2009) (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Ortenburger: Reception (2009) (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Ortenburger: Requests for Banners and Posters (2009) (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Ortenburger: Rubbing of sole of Leigh Ortenburger's Boot, for Visitors' Log (2009) (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - The First Hebrew City: Early Tel Aviv Through the Eyes of the Eliasaf Robinson Collection (April 21 -- August 31, 2009) (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Tel Aviv: Banners and Backdrops (2009) (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Tel Aviv: Case Maps, as Installed (2009) (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Tel Aviv: Colors (2009) (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Tel Aviv: Digital Image Issues (2009) (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Tel Aviv: Essays and Labels (2009) (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Tel Aviv: Image Transfer Procedures (2009) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Tel Aviv: Item Lists (2009) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Tel Aviv: Pink Slips for Materials Pulled for Display (2009) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Tel Aviv: Poster (2009) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Tel Aviv: Production Schedule (2009) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Tel Aviv: Publication (2009) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Tel Aviv: Publicity (2009) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Tel Aviv: Typography (2009) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Recent Arrivals: Rare Books, Manuscripts, and Archives (September 21 -- December 31, 2009) Banners (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 1 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 2 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 3 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 4 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 5 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 6 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 7 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 8 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 9 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 10 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 11 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 12 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 13 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 14 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 15 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 16 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 17 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 18 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Recent Arrivals: Case 19 and 20 (2009) (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Recent Arrivals: Floor Plan (2009) (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Recent Arrivals: Notes, Instructions, Email (2009) (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Recent Arrivals: Postcard (2009) (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Recent Arrivals: Press Release and Publicity Images (2009) (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Recent Arrivals: Stolovich (2009) (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Dream Factory on the Nile: Posters and Memorabilia from the Golden Age of Egyptian Film (January 18 -- May 2, 2010) (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Egyptian Film: Case Maps and Floorplan (2010) (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Egyptian Film: Correspondence and Notes (2010) (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Egyptian Film: Facsimile/Poser Repros from Hi-Resolution Scans (2010) (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Egyptian Film: Label Text from David G. (2010) (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Egyptian Film: Imprint with D Giovacchini article on Egyptian Movie Posters (2010) (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Egyptian Film: Postcards (2010) (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Egyptian Film: Poster (2010) (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Egyptian Film: Proposal (2010) (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Egyptian Film: Publicity (2010) (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Egyptian Film: Text Files (2010) (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Egyptian Film: Thumbnail Images (2010) (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Mary Webb: Neglected Genius (May 17 -- August 29, 2010) Bill Bishop Banners and Illustrations (2010) (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Mary Webb: Bill Bishop Banners, JP Digital Imaging (2010) (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Mary Webb: Case Layouts (2010) (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Mary Webb: Case Maps (2010) (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Mary Webb: Catalogue (2010) (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Mary Webb: Clematisa and Percival (2010) (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Mary Webb: Crawfords Catalog (2010) (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Mary Webb: Label Copy (2010) (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Mary Webb: Misc Notes and Email (2010) (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Mary Webb: Postcard/Announcement (2010) (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Mary Webb: Poster (2010) (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Mary Webb: Poster Trials and Banners (2010) (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Mary Webb: Publicity (2010) (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Mary Webb: Reception (2010) (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Mary Webb: Shropshire Photo Thumbnails (2010) (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Mary Webb: Vol. 1 Thumbnails (2010) (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Mary Webb: Website (2010) (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Celebrating Mexico: The Grito de Dolores and the Mexican Revolution 1810|1910|2010 (September 20, 2010 -- January 16, 2011) Announcement (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Banners and Color Challenges (2010) (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case Lists and Floorplans (2010) (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 1, Intro (2010) (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 2, Prelude to Revolution (2010) (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 3, Literature for a Revolution, Mariano Azuela (2010) (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 4, Lit/Corridos (2010) (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 5, Women/Soldaderas (2010) (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 6, Prelude to Revolution/Railways (2010) (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 7, Troops on the Border (2010) (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 8, The American Imagination (2010) (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 9, Battles (2010) (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 10, Machinery of War (2010) (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 11, Zapata (2010) (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 12, Immigration (2010) (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 13, Intro to Exhibit/Independence (2010) (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 14, Duelling Virgins (2010) (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 15, Battles (2010) (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 16, Daily Life (2010) (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 17, Morelos and Hidalgo (2010) (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 18, Inturbide and Guerrero (2010) (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 19, Heroines (2010) (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Case 20, Heroes (2010) (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Autumn Press (2010) (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Bancroft Mexico Images (2010) (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Barcode (2010) (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Capital Offset, Estimate Specs, Correspondence, and Invoice (2010) (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Color Graphics (2010) (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Colors (2010) (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Copy Editing Issues and Correspondence; Corrections to Capital Offset Proof (2010) (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Cover (2010) (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Design and Layout (2010) (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Essay, Chowning (2010) (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Essay, Del Valle (2010) (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Essay, Ruffinelli (2010) (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Estimate Comparison (2010) (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Fold-down (2010) (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Image Selection (2010) (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- 6/15/10 mtg. w/ Jack Von Euw re: Layout, color descisions (2010) (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Old Page Mockups and Cover Ideas (2010) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Old Proofs (2010) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Page design (2010) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Sent to Capital Offset (2010) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Spanish Hyphenation (2010) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Stanford Mexico Images (2010) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Timeline and Checklist (2010) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Typefaces/Kimera Type Specimens (2010) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Catalog -- Watermark Press Estimate (2010) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Contents (2010) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Celebrating Mexico: DLSS Scans (2010) (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Exhibit for SF Public (2010) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Graphics (poster lettering, invitation) (2010) (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Hoover Mats (2010) (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Celebrating Mexico: 4/30/2010 Meeting (2010) (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Celebrating Mexico: 5/25/3010 Mtg. Notes (2010) (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Meeting Notes (2010) (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Press Release and Publicity (2010) (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Reception Invitation Mailing (2010) (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Reception Sept. 23, 2010 (2010) (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Celebrating Mexico: Rejects and Extras (2010) (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - The American Enlightenment: Treasures from the Stanford University Libraries (February 7 -- June 15, 2011) Caroline Winterer, Exhibit Planning and Email Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Enlightenment: Case Lists and Maps (2011) (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Enlightenment: Case Texts (2011) (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog - 1-14-11 Cap. Offset Proof -- corvex marked (2011) (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog -- Sent to Capital Offset 1-14-11 and 12-14-10 (2011) (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog -- Archive Copy and Figs (2011) (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog -- Cover Design (2011) (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog -- ISBN and Barcode (2011) (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog -- Layout (2011) (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog -- Planning (2011) (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog -- Press Check (2011) (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog -- Printing Estimate and Invoice (Capital Offset) (2011) (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Enlightenment: Catalog -- Typography (2011) (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Enlightenment: Color (exhibit graphics) (2011) (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Enlightenment: Exhibit Layout (2011) (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Enlightenment: February 17 Invitations (2011) (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Enlightenment: Gallery Banners and Backdrops (2011) (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Enlightenment: Grant Proposal (SICA) (Caroline Winterer) (2011) (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Enlightenment: Images, not Stanford's (2011) (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Enlightenment: Permissions and Credits (2011) (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Enlightenment: Publicity and Events (2011) (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Enlightenment: Reception and Catering (2011) (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Enlightenment: Scanning Requests (2011) (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Enlightenment: Web Pages (2011) (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Gilbert White Revisited: Case 18 Backdrop Image; Guest Book; and Misc. Mounted Graphics (2001) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Gilbert White Revisited: Photographs/Brigitte Carnochan (2001) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Ortenberger Exhibit Banners, 1/3 size (2009) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Polish Artists Book Exhibit Video and Audio Tapes (1997) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Votes for Women videos (1997) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Winters and Lewis: Prospectus Postcard (2000) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Winters and Lewis: Ink Mix for Label (2000) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Winters and Lewis: Production Notes (2000) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Winters and Lewis: 1 Deluxe #36, 1 Regular #141 (2000) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Winters and Lewis: Working Proofs (2000) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Since the Three Millionth Book (1972) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Garrick's London (1969) (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Files of Margaret Kimball, Accession ARCH_2010_096
  - Post Earthquake – immediate (issues), 1989-90 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Space, 1995-97 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Space, SAL maintenance, 1993-96 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Collections – outside Green – 1993-95 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Space/Security, 1995-96 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - B160/Mezzanine/Newark, 1986-2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Green East/SAL – negotiations, etc., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Processing space 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Green West – Fall 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stacks – Field/Barchas, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Green West – program documents 1994-99 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Green West – SPEC 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - [Room] 341 redo 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Green West planning 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Space – Bldg. 160, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - SAL3 move planning 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Stegner event 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Stegner book – background materials (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Stegner book – Yolla Bolly Press to do 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Stegner book – memos, notes, etc. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Stegner book - mss (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Stegner book – foreword, colophon, acknowledgements copyright – final copy (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - LSCA [Library Services and Construction Act] – grant documents, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - CA State Library – LSCA – possible grant 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - LSCA current work (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - State project (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - CA State Library – Proposal 1989/90 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Reorganization 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - F. Shasky – collection offers 1993-94 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Special Collections Program Review 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Paul Radin Ppaers – Helene Hagan; acq. turned down 1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - EPA [Stauffer Chemical records use] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Statistical Info 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Six Millionth book 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Tanenbaum Librarian – Lynne Vieth Sept. 1998-June 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - GW Reopening Exhibit (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Meeting notes 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Green West furniture, phones (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Field Room 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - GW 1919 Booklet – Peter Koch reprint (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Green West – Information compiled Jan. 1995 for HABS report (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bender Room Exhibit (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Green West – events 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Green West documents to review 1991-92 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Green West Building Project 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Green West Renovation 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - MOA II 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sanchez Project 1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - SDF Research Grant 1989-1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - NSF Grant 1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Levertov exhibit – Art Gallery, Fall 1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Sterling Papers Project 1988-1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Conservation 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Budget 1991/92 – info on expenses (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Gifts 1992/93 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Gifts 1991/92 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Gifts 1990/91 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Selected Acq. List 1989/90 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Upstairs, Downstairs [department newsletter] 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Stanford Museum – list of borrowed items 1989-1996 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - David Lavender’s papers [not acquired] 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Centennial Events, 1991 Sep/Oct (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Time Capsule (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Centennial Follow-Up (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Founders Day formal program including slideshow, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Founders Day slideshow, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Founders Day - related events, project (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association slideshow (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - L H Hoover - dramatic reading (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - J L Stanford - dramatic reading (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CCOC Exhibit - Lasting Impact (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Centennial Exhibit - memorabilia (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Centennial Catalogue (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Centennial Weekend Exhibits (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dime Novel Project (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Eidenberger Etchings (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Trotting Horse Hall of Fame (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Historic Values Index (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Photograph Collections - Special Collections (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Simonds - Steinbeck article (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Collection of German, Austrian, and Swiss Culture (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Potential Administrative Transfers (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous files (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Manuscript Division Reference Files, circa 1960s-1990s; Accession ARCH_2011_073; 7.5 Linear Feet; (5 boxes)
  - A - Miscellaneous Reference (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Ansel (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adams, J. (M2, M104) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Addams, J. (M131) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aerospace (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aguilar (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alaska Commerical Co. (JL6) (Box 1, Folder 7)